Contact

rlqomallon@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rosanna-o-mallon-61b3b3b3 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Patient Safety

Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR)

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

PALS

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

CEN

Rosanna O'Mallon

BSN, RN, CEN

Staten Island, New York

Summary

Experienced Certified Emergency Registered nurse with a strong work ethic and a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Dedicated to working quickly and effectively under pressure to provide compassionate, comprehensive, collaborative and high-quality care to patients in a fast paced, high volume, 700+ bed level I trauma center.

Experience

Maimonides Medical Center
11 years 11 months

Registered Nurse May 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month) Emergency Department

Registra

July 2008 - April 2016 (7 years 10 months) Brooklyn, NY

Education

CUNY School of Professional Studies

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2018)

City University of New York-College of Staten Island
Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2015)